Guide to the University of Utah football video collection 1948-1999
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Coach's films: games, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii special teams, 1990 September 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1693-1694)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1990 September 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1695-1696)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1990 September 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1697-1699)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming special teams, 1990 September 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1700-1702)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1990 October 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1703-1706)
    3 wide, 1 end zone
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1990 October 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1707-1708)
    Wide, unlabeled
  - Utah vs. Colorado State special teams, 1990 October 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1709-1710)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, defense, special teams, 1990 October 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1711)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1990 October 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1712-1714)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1990 October 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1715-1716)
  - Utah vs. UTEP special teams, 1990 October 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1717-1719)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1990 October 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1720)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1990 October 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1721-1723)
    3 wide
  - Utah vs. Air Force special teams, 1990 October 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1724-1726)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1990 November 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1727-1729)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1990 November 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1731-1732)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State special teams, 1990 November 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1733-1734)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, special teams, 1990 November 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1735)
- Coach's films: games, 1990-1991 (Box 75)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1990 November 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1736)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1990 November 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1737-1738)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1990 November 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1739)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico special teams, 1990 November 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1740-1741)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, defense, special teams, 1990 November 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1742)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1990 November 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1743-1745)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1990 November 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1746-1747)
  - Utah vs. BYU special teams, 1990 November 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1748-1750)
    1 end zone, 2 wide
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, defense, special teams, 1991 August 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1751-1752)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, defense, special teams, 1991 September 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1753)
  - Utah vs. Arizona offense, defense, special teams, 1991 October 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1754)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, defense, special teams, 1991 October 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1755)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, defense, special teams, 1991 October 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1755-1757)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State, 1991 October 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1758)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, defense, special teams, 1991 October 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1759)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1991 October 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1760)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, defense, special teams, 1991 November 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1761-1762)
    2 end zone
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, defense, special teams, 1991 November 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1763-1764)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, defense, special teams, 1991 November 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1765)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1991 November 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1766)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, defense, special teams, 1991 November 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1767-1768)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1991 November 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1769-1770)
  - University of Utah highlights, 1991; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1771)
- Coach's films: games, 1992-1993 (Box 76)
  - 100 years of Utah football, 1992; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1772)
    Documents the history of the University of Utah football program 1892-1992
  - Utah vs. Nebraska offense, defense, special teams, 1992 September 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1773-1774)
  - Utah vs. Nebraska offense, 1992 September 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1775)
    From Nebraska
  - Utah vs. Nebraska defense, 1992 September 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1776)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, defense, special teams, 1992 September 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1777)
  - Utah vs. Oregon State offense, defense, special teams, 1992 September 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1778)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, defense, special teams, 1992 October 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1779)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, defense, special teams, 1992 October 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1780-1781)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, defense, special teams, 1992 October 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1782-1783)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, defense, special teams, 1992 October 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1784)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, defense, special teams, 1992 November 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1785)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, defense, special teams, 1992 November 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1786)
  - Utah vs. Washington State offense, defense, special teams, 1992 December 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1787)
  - Utah vs. Washington State special teams, 1992 December 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1788)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, defense, special teams, 1993 September 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1789)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1993 September 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1790)
    Wide and end zone
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1993 September 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1791)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, defense, special teams, 1993 September 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1792-1793)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1993 September 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1794)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1993 September 11; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1795)
  - Utah vs. Kansas offense, defense, special teams, 1993 September 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1796-1797)
  - Utah vs. Kansas special teams, 1993 September 18; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1798)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, defense, special teams, 1993 September 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1799-1801)
    1 wide, 2 end zone
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1993 September 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1802-1803)
    Wide, wide and end zone
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1993 September 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1804)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming special teams, 1993 September 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1805-1806)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense and special teams, 1993 September 25; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1807)
  - Utah vs. Idaho offense, defense, special teams, 1993 October 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1808-1809)
  - Utah vs. Idaho offense, 1993 October 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1810-1811)
    End zone and wide, Wide
  - Utah vs. Idaho defense, 1993 October 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1812)
  - Utah vs. Idaho special teams, 1993 October 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1813)
- Coach's films: games, 1993 (Box 77)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, defense, special teams, 1993 October 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1814-1816)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1993 October 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1817)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1993 October 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1818-1819)
    End zone and wide, wide
  - Utah vs. New Mexico special teams, 1993 October 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1820)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense and special teams, 1993 October 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1821)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, defense, special teams, 1993 October 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1822-1823)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1993 October 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1824)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1993 October 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1825)
  - Utah vs. UTEP special teams, 1993 October 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1826)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, defense, special teams, 1993 October 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1827-1828)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1993 October 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1829)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1993 October 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1830)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State special teams, 1993 October 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1831)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, defense, special teams, 1993 October 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1832-1833)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1993 October 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1834)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State special teams, 1993 October 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1835)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, defense, special teams, 1993 November 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1836-1837)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1993 November 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1838)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii special teams, 1993 November 06; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1839)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, defense, special teams, 1993 November 13; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1840-1842)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1993 November 13; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1843-1844)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1993 November 13; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1845-1846)
  - Utah vs. Air Force special teams, 1993 November 13; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1847)
  - Utah vs. BYU special teams, 1993 November 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1848)
- Coach's films: games, 1993 (Box 78)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1993 November 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1849-1850)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1993 November 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1851-1852)
  - Utah vs. University of Southern California (USC) offense, defense, special teams, 1993 December 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1853)
  - Utah vs. USC offense, 1993 December 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1854)
  - Utah vs. USC defense, 1993 December 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1855)
    Wide, end zone and wide
  - Utah vs. USC special teams, 1993 December 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1856)
- Coach's films: games, 1994 (Box 79)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1994 September 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1857-1858)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1994 September 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1859-1864)
    3 wide, 2 tight, 1 unknown
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1994 September 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1865)
    Tight
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, defense, kicking, 1994 September 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1866)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1994 September 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1867)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State offense, 1994 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1868-1873)
    1 wide and tight, 2 wide, 2 tight
  - Utah vs. Idaho State defense, 1994 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1874-1877)
    1 wide and tight, 1 wide, 2 tight
  - Utah vs. Idaho State kicking, 1994 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1878-1882)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State offense and kicking, 1994 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1883)
    Wide and tight
  - Utah vs. Idaho State offense, defense, kicking, 1994 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1884)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State, 1994 September 10; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1885)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1994 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1886-1887)
    Wide, tight
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1994 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1888-1890)
    Wide, tight, wide and tight
  - Utah vs. Oregon kicking, 1994 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1891-1892)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1994 September 17; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1893-1894)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1994 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1895-1896)
    End zone, tight
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1994 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1897-1898)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1994 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1899)
- Coach's films: games, 1994 (Box 80)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1994 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1900)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1994 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1901-1904)
    2 tight, 1 wide, 1 wide and tight
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1994 September 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1905-1906)
    2 wide and tight
  - Utah vs. San Diego State, 1994 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1907-1909)
    2 wide, 1 tight
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1994 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1910-1914)
    2 wide, 2 tight, 1 unknown
  - Utah vs. San Diego State defense, 1994 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1915-1919)
    2 wide, 2 tight, 1 wide and tight
  - Utah vs. San Diego State kicking, 1994 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1920-1921)
    1 wide, 2 tight
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense and kicking, 1994 October 08; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1922-1923)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii, 1994 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1924-1925)
    1 wide, 1 tight
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense, 1994 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1926-1927)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii defense, 1994 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1928-1930)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii kicking, 1994 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1931-1934)
    2 wide, 2 tight
  - Utah vs. Hawaii offense and kicking, 1994 October 15; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1935)
- Coach's films: games, 1994 (Box 81)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1994 October 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1936-1937)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State defense, 1994 October 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1938-1940)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State kicking, 1994 October 22; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1940-1941)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1994 October 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1942)
  - Utah vs. UTEP kicking, 1994 October 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1943-1944)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1994 October 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1945-1947)
    Camera master end zone, camera master wide, WAC end zone
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1994 November 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1948)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1994 November 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1949)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1994 November 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1950)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1994 November 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1951-1952)
    Camera master end zone, camera master wide
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1994 November 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1953)
    INT
  - Utah vs. Air Force kicking, 1994 November 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1954-1955)
    End zone, sideline
  - Utah vs. Air Force, 1994 November 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1956-1957)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1994 December 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1958)
  - Utah vs. Arizona offense, 1994 December 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1959)
- Coach's films: games, 1995 (Box 82)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1995 September 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1960-1961)
    INT, sideline
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1995 September 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1962)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1995 September 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1963-1964)
  - Utah vs. Stanford offense, 1995 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1965)
  - Utah vs. Stanford defense, 1995 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1966)
  - Utah vs. Stanford kicking, 1995 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1967)
  - Utah vs. Stanford, 1995 September 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1968-1969)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1995 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1970)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1995 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1971)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1995 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1972)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1995 September 16; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1973-1974)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State, 1995 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1975-1976)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State kicking, 1995 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1977-1978)
    2 INT
  - Utah vs. Fresno State offense, defense, kicking, 1995 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1979)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1995 September 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1980-1981)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State, 1995 September 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1982-1983)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State, 1995 October 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1984-1985)
  - Utah vs. Air Force, 1995 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1986-1987)
  - Utah vs. Air Force defense, 1995 October 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1988)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1995 October 28; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1989-1990)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1995 November 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1991-1992)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1995 November 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1993)
    Sideline
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1995 November 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1994)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1995 November 04; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1995)
  - Squash it NCAA promo with Chris Fuamatu-Ma'afala, circa 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1996)
- Coach's films: games, 1996-1998 (Box 83)
  - John Frank, circa 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1997)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1996 August 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1998-1999)
    Camera master wide, camera master tight
  - Utah vs. Stanford, 1996 September 07; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2000-2001)
    Camera master wide, camera master end zone
  - Utah vs. Southern Methodist University (SMU), 1996 September 14; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2002)
    Camera master end zone
  - Utah vs. Fresno State, 1996 September 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2003-2004)
  - Utah vs. Kansas, 1996 September 28; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2005-2006)
    Camera master wide, camera master end zone and tight
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1996 October 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2007-2008)
  - Utah vs. Texas Christian University (TCU), 1996 October 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2009-2010)
    Camera master wide sideline, camera master end zone
  - Utah vs. Tulsa, 1996 October 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2011-2012)
  - Utah vs. Rice, 1996 November 02; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2013-2014)
    Camera master end zone, camer master sideline
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1996 November 09; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2015-2016)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1996 November 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2017)
    INT, end zone and wide
  - Utah vs. Wisconsin, 1996 December 27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2018)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1997 November 20; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2019)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1998 September 05; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2020-2021)
    Camera master end zone, camer master wide
  - Utah vs. Louisville, 1998 September 12; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2022)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii, 1998 September 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2023)
  - Utah vs. Boise State, 1998 September 26; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2024-2025)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1998 October 03; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2026)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State, 1998 October 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2027-2028)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State, 1998 October 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2029-2030)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1998 November 07; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2031-2032)
  - Utah vs. BYU, 1998 November 21; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2033)
- Coach's films: digital duplucates, 1934-1997 (Box 84-85)
  Copies of University of Utah football games on DVD and Mini-DV
- Coach's films: digital duplucates and old game films, 1934-1996 (Box 86)
  Copies of University of Utah football games on DVD and Mini-DV and 16mm films of games 1934-1949
  - Utah vs. Utah Agricultural College (Utah State), 1934 November 29; 16mm film (Reel 2034)
    Highlights and halftime show featuring presentation of sweaters to original University of Utah football team, including Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints President David O. McKay
  - Utah vs. Idaho, 1948 September 25; 16mm film (Reel 2035-2037)
  - Utah vs. Arizona, 1948 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 2038)
  - Utah vs. Colorado, 1949 October 29; 16mm film (Reel 2039)
  - Utah vs. Denver, 1949; 16mm film (Reel 2040-2043)
- Coach's films: games (offense), 1987-1999 (Box 87)
  - Utah football, 1987; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2044)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1992; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2045)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2046)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2047)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2048)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2049)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2050)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2051)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2052)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2053)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2054)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2055)
  - Utah vs. Air Force offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2056)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2057)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2058)
  - Utah vs. Colorado State offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2059)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State offense, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2060)
  - Utah vs. Rice offense, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2061)
  - Utah vs. Tulsa offense, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2062)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2063)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2064)
  - Utah vs. Boise State offense, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2065)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2066)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2067)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State offense, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2068)
  - Utah vs. UNLV offense, 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2069)
  - Utah vs. Washington State offense, 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2070)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State offense, 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2071)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2072)
  - Utah vs. Boise State offense, 1999; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2073)
- Coach's films: games, 1993-1998 (Box 88)
  - Utah football highlights, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2074)
  - Utah vs. BYU, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2075-2077)
  - Utah vs. Air Force, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2078)
  - Utah vs. Kansas, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2079)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2080-2081)
  - Utah vs. Idaho, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2082)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2083-2084)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State, 1993; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2085)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2086)
  - Utah vs. Idaho State, 1994; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2087)
  - Utah vs. Stanford, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2088)
  - Utah vs. San Diego State, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2089)
  - Utah vs. BYU, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2090)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2091)
  - Utah vs. Tulsa, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2092)
  - Utah vs. Florida State, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2093)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2094)
  - Utah vs. Stanford, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2095)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1997; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2096)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1997; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2097)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1997; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2098)